CONTACT INFO

Phone

203-644-9813

Email

perrinbrown@optonline.net

LinkedIn

/perrin-brown

Website

perrinbrown.com

Github

/perrinbrown129

Location

Greater NYC Area

SKILLS

Languages

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, MongoDB, SQL

Softwares

WordPress, Photoshop,
Google Analytics & Adwords,
Zoho, Unleashed,
Dropbox, Smartsheet,
Stitchlabs, Klaviyo, Metrilo,
Constant Contact,
Mailchimp, Microsoft Office,
Canva

Social Media

Facebook, Twitter, Tumblr, Instagram, Pinterest

INTERESTS

LGBTQ+ advocacy, gluten-free food, ice hockey, field hockey & puzzles

Perrin Brown

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE:

Proactive Software Engineer with background in e-commerce and publicity, passionate about building and supporting teams. With skills in research and analysis, can creatively problem solve and organize data succinctly. Aims to work at a user-focused and inclusive company making an impact on the world.

WORK EXPERIENCE

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

SEI Fellow | September 2019-December 2019

- Learned full-stack web development at General Assembly's immersive program and expanded technical toolkit by learning HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, RESTful APIs, jQuery, Node.js, React.js, SQL, GitHub and Heroku to build a portfolio of web apps.

BULLDOG YOGA

E-Commerce Business Development Associate | August 2017-August 2019

- Increased social media engagement & sales by partnering with 100+ influencers, podcasts, blogs, businesses & subscription boxes
- Engaged with customers for technical support at all times, designed marketing emails and coordinated press releases

BODHI TREE LLC

Editorial Assistant | April 2016-June 2017

- Helped launch a metaphysical book store's website while managing "Journal" writers and researching article ideas
- Worked in WordPress CMS to configure landing pages, upload articles, enhance $\ensuremath{\mathsf{UX}}$ and $\ensuremath{\mathsf{SEO}}$

NAPA VALLEY FILM FESTIVAL

Hospitality Assistant | August 2015-January 2016

- Organized local housing for over 100 filmmakers & industry representatives associated with 50+ films
- Designed itineraries & welcome packages for filmmakers, while communicating with their representatives

EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY

Software Engineering Immersive | December 2019

VENTURE FOR AMERICA

Fellow, VFA WMN Leader & Entrepreneur | August 2017

DARTMOUTH COLLEGE

B.A. Asian & Middle Eastern Studies | June 2015